{"sid": "C9EPRM6Y0FKS_main", "calc_equals_delay": 3, "block_data": {"block_0": {"mean_level": 7, "start_time": 390630, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "300", "question_time_start": 390632, "question": "4+3+8+98", "correct_answer": 113, "events": [["calc_1", 398850], ["calc_5", 399551], ["calc_+", 401110], ["calc_9", 401241], ["calc_8", 401706], ["calc_=", 402506], ["submit", 408648]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "283", "answered_time": 408648, "user_answer": "113", "user_correct": "True", "score": "1"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "283", "question_time_start": 408650, "question": "7+3+7+68", "correct_answer": 85, "events": [["submit", 416229]], "time_left_end": "278", "answered_time": 416229, "user_answer": "85", "user_correct": "True", "score": "2"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "278", "question_time_start": 416235, "question": "3+79+88", "correct_answer": 170, "events": [["submit", 431164]], "time_left_end": "263", "answered_time": 431164, "user_answer": "170", "user_correct": "True", "score": "3"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "263", "question_time_start": 431166, "question": "16+786", "correct_answer": 802, "events": [["submit", 441668]], "time_left_end": "253", "answered_time": 441668, "user_answer": "792", "user_correct": "False", "score": "2"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "253", "question_time_start": 441673, "question": "23+37", "correct_answer": 60, "events": [["submit", 447282]], "time_left_end": "248", "answered_time": 447282, "user_answer": "60", "user_correct": "True", "score": "3"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "248", "question_time_start": 447283, "question": "3+44+28", "correct_answer": 75, "events": [["calc_4", 454034], ["calc_7", 454922], ["calc_+", 455682], ["calc_2", 456668], ["calc_8", 457415], ["calc_=", 458247], ["submit", 462748]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "232", "answered_time": 462748, "user_answer": "75", "user_correct": "True", "score": "4"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "232", "question_time_start": 462750, "question": "3+7+4+24", "correct_answer": 38, "events": [["submit", 468765]], "time_left_end": "226", "answered_time": 468765, "user_answer": "38", "user_correct": "True", "score": "5"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "226", "question_time_start": 468766, "question": "76+47", "correct_answer": 123, "events": [["submit", 479318]], "time_left_end": "217", "answered_time": 479318, "user_answer": "123", "user_correct": "True", "score": "6"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "217", "question_time_start": 479325, "question": "9+3+13", "correct_answer": 25, "events": [["submit", 487351]], "time_left_end": "209", "answered_time": 487351, "user_answer": "25", "user_correct": "True", "score": "7"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "209", "question_time_start": 487355, "question": "9+4+59", "correct_answer": 72, "events": [["submit", 499367]], "time_left_end": "197", "answered_time": 499367, "user_answer": "72", "user_correct": "True", "score": "8"}}}, "block_1": {"mean_level": 7, "start_time": 499368, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "197", "question_time_start": 499368, "question": "4+29+89", "correct_answer": 122, "events": [["submit", 513610]], "time_left_end": "183", "answered_time": 513610, "user_answer": "122", "user_correct": "True", "score": "9"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "183", "question_time_start": 513616, "question": "9+7+8+14", "correct_answer": 38, "events": [["calc_2", 523770], ["submit", 527733]], "time_left_end": "169", "answered_time": 527733, "user_answer": "38", "user_correct": "True", "score": "10"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "169", "question_time_start": 527735, "question": "39+87", "correct_answer": 126, "events": [["calc_C", 529232], ["submit", 540351]], "time_left_end": "157", "answered_time": 540351, "user_answer": "126", "user_correct": "True", "score": "11"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "157", "question_time_start": 540354, "question": "9+7+6+94", "correct_answer": 116, "events": [["submit", 548264]], "time_left_end": "149", "answered_time": 548264, "user_answer": "116", "user_correct": "True", "score": "12"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "149", "question_time_start": 548265, "question": "66+438", "correct_answer": 504, "events": [["submit", 559515]], "time_left_end": "138", "answered_time": 559515, "user_answer": "504", "user_correct": "True", "score": "13"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "138", "question_time_start": 559516, "question": "6+8+8+93", "correct_answer": 115, "events": [["submit", 574946]], "time_left_end": "123", "answered_time": 574946, "user_answer": "115", "user_correct": "True", "score": "14"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "123", "question_time_start": 574948, "question": "9+6+84", "correct_answer": 99, "events": [["submit", 580067]], "time_left_end": "118", "answered_time": 580067, "user_answer": "99", "user_correct": "True", "score": "15"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "118", "question_time_start": 580068, "question": "6+37+16", "correct_answer": 59, "events": [["submit", 591481]], "time_left_end": "106", "answered_time": 591481, "user_answer": "59", "user_correct": "True", "score": "16"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "106", "question_time_start": 591483, "question": "37+44", "correct_answer": 81, "events": [["submit", 612166]], "time_left_end": "87", "answered_time": 612166, "user_answer": "81", "user_correct": "True", "score": "17"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "87", "question_time_start": 612169, "question": "6+6+13", "correct_answer": 25, "events": [["submit", 619403]], "time_left_end": "79", "answered_time": 619403, "user_answer": "25", "user_correct": "True", "score": "18"}}}, "block_2": {"mean_level": 7, "start_time": 619403, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "79", "question_time_start": 619403, "question": "6+28+66", "correct_answer": 100, "events": [["submit", 633487]], "time_left_end": "66", "answered_time": 633487, "user_answer": "100", "user_correct": "True", "score": "19"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "66", "question_time_start": 633492, "question": "38+883", "correct_answer": 921, "events": [["calc_8", 641472], ["calc_3", 642201], ["calc_+", 642902], ["calc_3", 643471], ["calc_8", 644277], ["calc_3", 649581], ["calc_C", 651599], ["calc_C", 652312], ["calc_C", 652776], ["calc_C", 652779], ["calc_C", 652783], ["calc_3", 654061], ["calc_8", 654792], ["calc_+", 656196], ["calc_8", 658205], ["calc_3", 659016], ["calc_=", 659847], ["submit", 665599]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "37", "answered_time": 665599, "user_answer": "921", "user_correct": "True", "score": "20"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "37", "question_time_start": 665605, "question": "6+3+7+37", "correct_answer": 53, "events": [["submit", 677382]], "time_left_end": "26", "answered_time": 677382, "user_answer": "53", "user_correct": "True", "score": "21"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "26", "question_time_start": 677385, "question": "4+6+4+24", "correct_answer": 38, "events": [["submit", 684565]], "time_left_end": "19", "answered_time": 684565, "user_answer": "38", "user_correct": "True", "score": "22"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "19", "question_time_start": 684569, "question": "79+97", "correct_answer": 176, "events": [["submit", 697231]], "time_left_end": "6", "answered_time": 697231, "user_answer": "176", "user_correct": "True", "score": "23"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "6", "question_time_start": 697232, "question": "9+6+9+28", "correct_answer": 52, "events": []}}}}}